{

    "init": {
            "prompt": "Would you like to...\n[n] Make a new dead drop.\n[v] View a dead drop.\n [e] Edit a dead drop.\n [d] Delete a dead drop.",
            "inputHistory": [],
            "validResponse": ["n", "v", "e", "d"]
        },
    "message": [
        {
            "prompt": "Enter your dead drop a title.",
            "inputHistory": ["n"],
            "validResponse": ["title"]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "Please enter your desired message.",
            "inputHistory": ["n", "title"],
            "validResponse": ["msg"]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "Your message has been staged, now enter your desired password",
            "inputHistory": ["n", "title", "msg"],
            "validResponse": ["psw"]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "Would you like to add an attachment [y/n]?",
            "inputHistory": ["n", "title", "msg", "psw"],
            "validResponse": ["attachment"]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "Your dead drop is staged, type [s] to send your dead-drop mesage",
            "inputHistory": ["n", "title", "msg", "psw", "attachment"],
            "validResponse": ["s", "sendNewDeaddrop"]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "Encrypting",
            "inputHistory": ["n", "title", "msg", "psw", "attachment", "s"],
            "validResponse": ["none"]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "Please input the message ID of the message you would like to view",
            "inputHistory": ["v"],
            "validResponse": ["msgId"]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "Your message has been staged, please input the correct password",
            "inputHistory": ["v", "msgId"],
            "validResponse": ["psw"]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "Your password is set, type [s] to view the dead-drop message",
            "inputHistory": ["v", "msgId", "psw"],
            "validResponse": ["s", "sendViewMessage"]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "Decrypting",
            "inputHistory": ["v", "msgId", "psw", "s"],
            "validResponse": ["none"]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "Please input the message ID of the message you would like to delete",
            "inputHistory": ["d"],
            "validResponse": ["msgId"]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "Your message has been staged for deletion, please input the correct password",
            "inputHistory": ["d", "msgId"],
            "validResponse": ["psw"]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "Password verified, type [s] to delete the dead-drop message",
            "inputHistory": ["d", "msgId", "psw"],
            "validResponse": ["s", "sendDeleteMessage"]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "Deleting",
            "inputHistory": ["d", "msgId", "psw", "s"],
            "validResponse": ["none"]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "Pleases input the message ID of the message you would like to edit",
            "inputHistory": ["e"],
            "validResponse": ["msgId"]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "Please input the correct password",
            "inputHistory": ["e", "msgId"],
            "validResponse": ["psw"]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "Password verified, type your new title",
            "inputHistory": ["e", "msgId", "psw"],
            "validResponse": ["title"]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "Type your new message",
            "inputHistory": ["e", "msgId", "psw", "title"],
            "validResponse": ["msg"]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "Would you like to change or add an attachment [y/n]?",
            "inputHistory": ["e", "msgId", "psw", "title", "msg"],
            "validResponse": ["attachment"]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "Your updated message has been staged, press [s] to submit.",
            "inputHistory": ["e", "msgId", "psw", "title", "msg", "attachment"],
            "validResponse": ["s", "sendEditMessage"]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "Encrypting update",
            "inputHistory": ["e", "msgId", "psw", "title", "msg", "attachment", "s"],
            "validResponse": ["none"]
        }
    ]    
}